(Leonard:)What is going on?
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Uh, I need to keep my anxiety
at the right level,
(Sheldon:)so I'm using Darth Vader,
the Joker, and Godzilla's roar
(Sheldon:)to keep me in that sweet spot.
(Sheldon:)Uh, I tried including
Taylor Swift in the mix,
(Sheldon:)but turns out I love her.
(Leonard:)Well, at least listen to it
through headphones.
(Leonard:)I'm trying to sleep.
Good night.
Boy!
(Sheldon:)Taylor was right-- haters gonna
hate, hate, hate, hate, hate.
(Amy:)You've been working
so much lately,
(Amy:)I'm glad you didn't forget
about date night.
(Sheldon:)Of course.
(Leonard:)Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Amy:)Maybe you want to put the
notebook away and talk to me.
(stammers)
I can do both.
No, my brain is working
at optimal capacity.
No, I can have
a conversation with you